http://www.goldrefiner.com/privacy-policy

Home/
About Us/About UsMeet Our TeamOur PartnersShippingFAQSitemap
Industries We Serve/
What We Recycle & Refine/Precious Metals We Recycle & RefinePrecious MetalsPlatinumPalladiumGoldSilverElectronics
Privacy Policy
Read the Privacy Policy for Specialty Metals, the top choice in the US for secondary refining of Gold, Silver, Platinum, Palladium, Rhodium and Electronics scrap for over 32 years.
Home/
About Us/About UsMeet Our TeamOur PartnersShippingFAQSitemap
Industries We Serve/
What We Recycle & Refine/Precious Metals We Recycle & RefinePrecious MetalsPlatinumPalladiumGoldSilverElectronics
Individuals Buy & Sell/
Blog/
Contact Us/
Call Us: 800-426-2344/
Questions? Call us at 800-426-2344.Effective 01/01/14Our Commitment To PrivacyAt Specialty Metals Smelters & Refiners, LLC, your privacy is as important to us today as it has been for the last 32 years. Specialty Metals has been the top choice in the US for secondary refining of Gold, Silver and Platinum Group Metals, for our clients in the industrial, electronic, jewelry and mining sectors, and one reason is that we value and protect your privacy and the privacy of your transactions to the extent the law allows.Because of our commitment to transparency and to better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining Specialty Metals’ online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.To make this notice easy to find, we link to it from every page of our website as well as anywhere personally identifiable information may be requested.We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.The Information We Collect:This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Specialty Metals Smelters & Refiners, LLC website.We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.SpecialtyMetals.com collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number only when you provide it. We also collect additional applicable information when you fill out our forms, which include but are not limited to:Contact Us FormAnti-Money Laundering Campaign Form for IndividualsAnti-Money Laundering Campaign Form for BusinessesMaterials Submission Form/Packing ListSpecialty Metals Smelters & Refiners, LLC also uses analytics programs to collect non-personally identifiable information about you.You may choose not to provide the personal information requested, in which case your access to these items will be restricted.Specialty Metals Smelters & Refiners, LLC will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.SpecialtyMetals.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from SpecialtyMetals.com so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the SpecialtyMetals.com Web site.The Way We Use Information:Personal information collected by SpecialtyMetals.com is used solely for the purpose of purchasing, processing, billing and shipping your purchases.We do not share this information with outside parties except when required by law or for other legal reasons.If you choose to opt-in to receive communications or notifications from us, we will only use the information you provide to deliver the communications for which you opted in. As your communications may be delivered using a third party, such as an email service provider, we may transfer your information to that party to be used exclusively for that purpose and not to be used in any other way.We use return email addresses and other contact information you provide to communicate with you. Such information is not used for any other purpose and is not shared with outside parties unless specified in your communication to us.We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to optimize the user experience on our website.Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses, unless as required by law.Non-Personal InformationCertain non-personal information of visitors is also recorded by the standard operation of Specialty Metals’ Internet servers. This information is primarily used to provide visitors to Specialty Metals with an enhanced online experience. Information tracked includes the type of browser being used by the visitor, the type of operating system, and the domain name of the visitor's Internet service provider. Specialty Metals may disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe the Specialty Metals service to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.Use of CookiesCookies are web code that allow websites to display ads that relate to your interests and help measure advertising and site usage information in order to bring you a better user experience.We use cookies in order to bring you more relevant ads with Google Display and Search Advertising (e.g., Remarketing or Google Display Network Impression Reporting).We use third-party vendors, including Google, in order to show ads on sites across the Internet.Specialty Metals along with third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on past visits to our website and to report how ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site.Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising, customize Google Display Network ads using Ads Settings. Visit Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on to learn more.Cookies do not allow the website to access personal information that you haven't already provided.Our Commitment to Data SecurityWe will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.Our Commitment to Children's PrivacyProtecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.How You Can Access or Correct Your InformationYou can access any personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by emailing us at info@specialtymetals.com from the same email address you used when you purchased or registered. We will then send you an email with all of the personally identifiable information we have collected. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.To protect your privacy and security, in addition to the process outlined above, we may also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.How To Contact UsShould you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please visit our Contact Us page.
Privacy | Legal/Terms | Shipping | Anti-Money Laundering Campaign | Contact Us | List of Precious Metals | Industries Served
Copyright © 2019 Specialty Metals Smelters & Refiners LLCOffice/Shipping Address: 2490 Black Rock Turnpike, Fairfield, CT 06825 / Facility Address: 82 W. Clark St., West Haven, CT 06516
